[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Java is a",
    "options": [
      "High-level programming language",
      "Object-oriented (class-based) programming language",
      "Functional, imperative and reflective programming language",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is a correct syntax to output \"Hello World\" in Java?",
    "options": [
      "System.out.println(\"Hello World\");",
      "echo(\"Hello World\");",
      "Console.WriteLine(\"Hello World\");",
      "print(\"Hello World\");"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?",
    "options": [
      "/* This is a comment",
      "# This is a comment",
      "// This is a comment",
      "<-- This is a comment -->"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
    "options": ["myString", "string", "Txt", "String"],
    "correctAnswer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
    "options": ["float x = 5;", "num x = 5;", "int x = 5;", "x = 5;"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
    "options": ["float x = 2.8f;", "byte x = 2.8f;", "x = 2.8f;", "int x = 2.8f;"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which method can be used to find the length of a string?",
    "options": ["len()", "length()", "getLength()", "getSize()"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
    "options": ["toUpperCase()", "upperCase()", "toUpper()", "toUpperCaseString()"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which method can be used to return a string in lower case letters?",
    "options": ["toLowerCase()", "lowerCase()", "toLower()", "toLowerCaseString()"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
    "options": ["=", "==", "===", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a class in Java?",
    "options": ["class", "className", "myClass", "newClass"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?",
    "options": [
      "class myObj = new MyClass();",
      "new myObj = MyClass();",
      "MyClass myObj = new MyClass();",
      "class MyClass = new MyObj();"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?",
    "options": ["import", "extract", "package", "add"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
    "options": ["break", "exit", "stop", "return"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is the default value of data type boolean in Java?",
    "options": ["0", "1", "true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is the value of the expression 79 / 10?",
    "options": ["9", "7", "0", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is the value of the expression 79 % 10?",
    "options": ["9", "7", "0", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Which word is not a Java keyword?",
    "options": ["protect", "public", "private", "secret"],
    "correctAnswer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which data type is not a Java primitive data type?",
    "options": ["int", "char", "String", "boolean"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  }
]
